

Senior Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, System Programming, System Analysis, Agile Methodology with key expertise in c++(17)



Current Designation: Senior Engineer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 2 Month(s)

Current Company: L&T Technology Services Notice Period: 3 Months

Highest Degree:

Current Location: Pune

Pref. Location: Pune, Kochi, Ernakulam

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Senior Engineer, Software Developer, Agile Methodology, Devops, Azure, GIT, SQL, Python, C++, Data Structures

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

### **Summary**

I have overall 5 years of industrial experience in Medical vertical, business oriented Telecommunication -media as well as Safety critical Automotive domain. I am perceived as an energetic and committed person. I am looking for a job where I shall be able to put forward my skills to shape and develop the end deliverables with best results.

## **Work Experience**

# **L&T Technology Services** as Senior Engineer Apr 2020 to Till Date

Currently working as C++ developer , in Medical Domain for software modules responsible in Patient critical monitoring devices. Role involves in designing algorithms for Physiological paramters and implementing communication protocols.

\* Working in Agile framework team in C++ Language on Linux platform, gRPC Protocols , gTest, Azure Devops.

**Amdocs** as Software Developer Nov 2018 to Mar 2020

Amdocs DVCI, Pune Domain- Telecommunication & media Duration- Nov. 2018 - Mar 2020 Experience- 1.5 Year Designation - Software Developer Job Profile

Amdocs is leading software, services provider to communications, media, financial service companies, providing innovative solutions, intelligent operations and delivery.

Worked as C++ developer in Revenue Management team of Amdocs, where responsibilities involves in development of application for efficient bill designing, invoices, statements and letters based on business logic. Working on inhouse tools and scripts that deliver information to a large number of consumer and corporate customers. Part of team that follows Agile methodology and qualitative approach towards its delivery systems.

#### Knorr-Bremse Technology Center as Engineer

Sep 2015 to Nov 2018

Prev. Experience

Organisation- Knorr-Bremse Technology Center India, Domain- R&D in Automotive Duration- From September 2015 to Nov. 2018 Experience-3 Years and 2 months

Designation - Engineer

Job Profile

The Knorr-Bremse TCI is a German based MNC in Pune which is the world's leading manufacturer of braking systems and supplier of additional sub-systems for rail and commercial vehicles.

Had worked in the R&D team of Truck Department as C++ software Developer. Project involved development of modules for Hardware in a Loop (HIL) system which is used in the Truck bake simulations. The project helped to gain expertise over writing wrapper classes for RTOS based Ontime OS system, Kernel internals process scheduler, multithreading concepts, and Network protocols.

Responsibilities also involved requirement gathering from clients and support to the users of Simulator in India, Germany and Hungary.

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Pimpri Chinchwad College of Engineering in 2015

PG: in 0

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
C++ 17	11	2020	4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
С			1 Year(s)	
JAVA			0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
Angel script			1 Year(s)	
Dev Tool: Visual Studio	10	2018	3 Year(s) 3 Month(s)	
Dev Tool: Embarcadero RAD		2016	1 Year(s)	
Dev Tool:Linux		2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
Eclipse		0	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Malayalam				
Marathi				

#### **Affirmative Action**

**Work Authorization** 

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

**Employment Status: Full time**